antivirus-xp-pro-2009.com 2009-03-11

# Antivirus XP Pro

Privacy Policy

At Antivirus XP Pro , we deeply respect your online privacy and your need to protect Personal Information you share with us. This Privacy Policy covers the principles Antivirus XP Pro follows to keep the information we collect about you safe.

Visitor Information

We collect only the information we need to know in order to provide you with the services on our website, to process and fulfill your order and to notify you of your order status. This information may include your name, e-mail address, mailing address and credit card number. Sometimes we also can ask for additional information necessary to take part in sponsors contests and different promotion events

What we do with this information

Antivirus XP Pro requests the information to provide you with our services or make your visits to our site more enjoyable, and the information necessary for us to fulfill your order, to track the status of your order, and to provide the best customer service possible

It is against our Privacy Policy to sell your private information, such as e-mail address, to any third-party for its use in marketing or solicitation. Sometimes we will use the information provided to us to let you know about important changes made to our Web site or improvements regarding special offers.

Antivirus XP Pro has right to analyze the provided information for statistics to imply the knowledge received for further improvements in our services. These statistical data may also be provided to potential advertisers and/or business partners. This means that we will never disclose your personal information such as name, age or phone number, but statistical numbers only (not "Mr. John Doe, age 35, is from Dallas, Texas", but "15% of our users are from Texas").

What is a "cookie"?

"Cookies" are the small text files that a Web server sends to your Internet browser and which are stored on your computer's hard drive. We use "cookies" so you would not need to sign up for every page to receive our services. They also give us a possibility to gather information about your browsing preferences and to do some statistical research. You can set your browser to block "cookies" but it will make impossible for you to enjoy some of our services.

Your consent

By visiting and purchasing products through Antivirus XP Pro Web site, you consent to the terms of our Privacy Policy and to the collection and use of information by Antivirus XP Pro as specified above. In case if any changes are made to our privacy policy, they will be posted prominently on this page, so you can always be up to date on the information we collect and how we use it.
